Stay close to fellow fairies,
namely me.
Since we're precious stones,
we two have
a great deal in common.
Is that so?
I don't find us alike at all.
You're quite vigilant.
If you weren't,
you wouldn't survive for long.
From opal.
[birds chirp]
Comrades,
I'm glad to see you're all here!
What's this nonsense?
You're supposed to be helping
the artisans work.
[MITHRIL]
Excellent point!
For you see,
it is those very artisans
who are in desperate need
of rescue!
Why, you ask?
Because an evil ghost is lurking
within Holly Leaf Castle
as we speak!
[DAANA, HAL]
Huh?
- [sighs]
- [MITHRIL] But take heart!
Your lives are in my tiny
yet capable hands!
I'm forming a brigade
of ghost-hunting vigilantes!
We shall rout
that spirit forthwith!
[GLADUS]
Intriguing.
[gasps]
Please include me
in this brave endeavor.
[MITHRIL] Your name is Gladus,
right soldier?
[GLADUS] At your service,
Captain Mithril Lid Pod.
[MITHRIL] Oh, I wholeheartedly
accept your aid!
Huh?
You can't leave yet,
Challe fenn Challe!
We're going on a patrol!
- [CHALLE] I'll be in my room.
- [gasps]
Wait, don't go!
Without your help,
who's going to battle
the spirit to the death!
- That's your job, Captain.
- [grunts]
- [thuds]
- [groans]
- [stabs]
- [gasps]
[MITHRIL]
Oh, come on!
[exhales]
[scoffs]
[crickets chirp]
[ANNE]
I'll just put this away.
There.
That's enough for now.
Great work, everyone!
[ALL sigh]
[ANNE] Oh, right.
Mithril isn't sleeping in here.
He said he was ghost hunting.
Hmm.
I'm so tired.
- [door slams]
- [gasps]
- Beside you!
- Huh?
What, Challe?
Huh?
- [screams]
- [gasps]
Put on the lamp!
- [yells] What's happening?
- [boy] Stop that!
- [CHALLE] Do it now!
- [boy grunts] Let go of me!
[man grunts]
[ANNE]
Who is that?
- [CHALLE] The ghost.
- [ANNE] Ghost?
I am not a ghost, you fool!
Uh...
Oh no, he's dead!
Or is he?
I'm not sure
whether ghosts can die!
He fainted, that's all.
[ANNE]
Um, excuse me.
- [screams]
- I tricked you!
Oh, you poor idiots!
That's what you get
for letting me go!
[boy groans]
[gasps] What's wrong now!
Oh, Master.
I'm so sorry.
Who's his Master?
[ELLIOTT]
So, this is the big scary ghost
we've been hearing about?
[MITHRIL]
He's the root of the mystery?
[CHALLE]
All the footprints were his.
I'd say he's a fairy
who can pass through objects.
[ANNE] That explains
what happened to the locks.
[CHALLE] Last night,
he was on the first floor
playing tricks on the artisans,
so tonight,
I thought it'd be wise
to lie in wait for him
on the second floor.
[ANNE]
And what we thought was a ghost
turned out to be a young boy.
Huh?
[gasps]
We won't hurt you!
You're safe!
Would you tell us your name?
[boy]
I have no name to give a thief!
Thief!
You can't be referring to me!
[boy]
I am!
Just you wait,
I'll dispose of all of you!
Hey, I'm not letting you
talk to Anne that way!
I will have you know
the kingdom's religion gave us
explicit permission
to use this place.
So, the one who shouldn't
be here is probably you.
The church allowed you to stay?
What's that matter?
This castle belongs
to Lord Stewart's
younger brother.
Lord Herbert of House Chamber!
Does that make you...
I am Noah!
The devoted page
to Lord Herbert himself.
And his orders to me were clear!
I have been charged
with guarding his castle!
I see.
You said your name was Noah?
- That's right!
- The House Chamber?
But don't you know they were
cast out 15 years ago?
I mean,
this Lord Herbert person
is probably long dead by now.
- Don't you dare say he's dead!
[groans]
[NOAH] I know Lord Herbert is
coming home!
No matter how many years
it takes!
That's why I have
a responsibility
- to protect this castle!
- Hmm.
Sometime after your master
had departed,
your castle had been invaded
by Millsland troops, correct?
You're just a fairy who is
being controlled by a thief!
You'll never understand!
[gasps]
♪
It can't be!
We're travelling with this girl
because we choose to.
Now answer me,
Millsland soldiers came here,
isn't that right?
[NOAH]
Yes.
They rushed in
wearing filthy armor
destroying everything.
They ripped down
the crest of House Chamber,
shredded the portraits.
Any furniture
that bore the crest
was burned in the garden.
In the war,
did you think the royal family
defeated House Chamber?
What was the ending?
[NOAH] I thought that
House Chamber lost the war.
[ANNE]
Noah.
[ELLIOTT]
So, do you understand now?
The Millsland royal family
annexed this castle we're in.
In the end, it was donated
to the Church
of Saint Lewiston Bell.
And we're borrowing it
from the church.
That's why we're here.
I think you'll agree,
that hardly makes us thieves.
Well, even so,
I know it
as Lord Herbert's castle
and I have to protect it
until he returns.
That's what he asked of me,
and I won't disobey him.
But I just told you,
he's never coming back!
The man's as dead
as dead can be.
Stop saying that he's dead!
[groans]
I refuse to trust anyone
who assumes
that my master is dead
without any proof at all!
You're lying!
And I won't--
[grunts]
- [falling]
- [ANNE] Got you!
I'll make you pay.
I swear.
You're weak.
You're not eating, are you?
Hmm.
[birds chirp]
[ANNE]
Noah, please eat, just a bit.
[NOAH] If I want to stay here,
I can't eat anything
except what Lord Herbert gave
to me.
It was an order from my master.
[ANNE] He's only allowed to eat
what Lord Herbert gave him?
How could someone give
that order?
- [GLADUS] Anne, good morning.
- Huh?
Oh. Hello there.
How is the fairy
you discovered last night?
I mean, I--
Not well? What a shame.
[gasps]
What are--
A lovely aroma.
You smell of silver sugar.
Of course.
I think all the artisans here
carry that smell.
Most likely.
But yours,
is uniquely spectacular.
Um, well,
I should go!
There's work to do!
She's an adorable girl.
And she smells wonderful.
Don't you agree, Challe?
That scarecrow, adorable?
You've got odd taste.
You mean you don't
find her cute in the slightest?
[CHALLE]
No.
I see.
And yet she's the reason that
you're here, isn't that right?
You stay with her
because she's so dear
that you can't bear
to leave her side.
What a naive manner of thinking.
You never show
your feelings, do you?
You and I
are of the same origin.
So then, is it safe to assume
that we think in the same way?
I have no interest
in how you think.
Whether you take
any interest in it or not,
the fact is that you and I
are extremely close.
Our destinies
are bound together.
If that's your idea of a joke,
I'm not laughing.
Picture a darkened chapel.
There's a hole through one wall
and an altar positioned
at the very back.
There once were ornaments
adorning the entrance
but now the ceiling
and walls are scarred
with the signs of excavation.
How do you know that place?
It's exactly as I suspected.
If you'd show me
even the slightest hint
of your sincere feelings,
I'd happily tell you everything.
[CHALLE]
What? How does he know?
Who is he?
[GLEN]
Noah, did you say?
I'm worried that he might
starve himself to death.
[ANNE]
So am I.
He says
if he wants to stay here,
he's only allowed
to eat the food
that his master gave him
but I don't understand
why he doesn't just run away
and be free.
I assume it means
that his master left
- with Noah's wing in hand.
- [ANNE] Oh.
[GLEN]
The poor thing.
No wonder he keeps waiting
for a master
who will never return.
[ANNE] I see,
so that's why he won't leave.
Fairies desire
sugar confections.
Perhaps you could persuade him
to eat one of those.
Oh, you're right.
Then I'll try that!
[birds chirp]
I wonder if he's still awake.
Let's see.
Huh?
♪
- [ANNE] Noah?
- Huh?
- [NOAH] Oh, it's just the thief.
- [ANNE] What are you doing?
[ANNE]
This must be Lord Herbert.
Right.
That explains why
this one painting isn't dirty
like the rest of them.
Tell me.
Did Lord Herbert take your wing
with him
on the day
he departed the castle?
Of course not,
he's not a bad person!
He gave it back to me
before he left home!
What?
He didn't take it?
That's right!
[ANNE] Then why have you
stayed here for 15 years?
If you have your wing,
then you're free.
Are you dense?
As I've already told you,
I take Lord Herbert's wishes
very seriously
and I was the one ordered
to take care of the castle.
You're sure?
That's exactly what he told you?
Protect the castle, never leave,
and don't eat anything
that he didn't give to you?
[gasps] Well, I...
I just want to keep my word.
He said he wouldn't take me
with him into battle
and that I should look after
the castle while he's away.
Lord Herbert said it's something
only I could do.
But he also said
that once I've eaten
all the sugar confections,
- I should leave.
- [gasps]
If I ate anything else,
I wouldn't be allowed
to stay any longer.
[ANNE]
Wait a minute.
I see now.
He wanted him to run away.
So, Noah, did you eat
the sugar confections?
Only some!
But I left one final piece!
And that means I don't have
to leave the castle just yet!
I'll wait for Lord Herbert!
Noah...
That's a...
[ANNE] It's one of the snow
crystals we're making.
I asked if we could spare one.
I was hoping you'd eat it.
After all, I'm sure Lord Herbert
would prefer
that you were healthy
while waiting for him, so...
[NOAH]
I can't.
If I disobey, then I have
to leave the castle.
I'm sorry,
but I'm Lord Herbert's page.
- There's no choice.
- [ANNE] Noah.
[CHALLE]
How?
There's no reason he should be
talking about a place
that only Liz and I knew.
Unless...
- [thuds]
- [gasps]
[CHALLE]
What are you doing?
Oh, you're here.
♪
Thanks for your help.
Noah couldn't stand anymore.
I assumed he was light enough
to carry on my own.
- Is that for him?
- Mmm-hmm.
But he still wouldn't eat it.
And he told me that his master
gave him his wing back.
[CHALLE]
Oh?
[ANNE]
Mmm-hmm.
I think Lord Herbert must've
wanted him to leave this place.
That's the real reason
why he gave that order
but because of the promise
they made,
Noah's still waiting for him.
- You're a silver sugar master.
- Huh?
So, make something
that he likes,
something that he can
be convinced to eat.
You think I can?
You think I'm wrong?
No, you're not wrong.
[giggles]
♪
[grunts]
Huh?
What are you...
Did Gladus tell you anything?
[ANNE]
What?
I'm sorry. I don't know.
Did he?
He said that I smell
like silver sugar but...
[sighs]
[ANNE]
Challe?
[gasps]
Challe, I--
You're far too trusting.
Are you saying
that he's dangerous?
Perhaps.
So don't let your guard down.
Right.
[gasps]
- Good girl.
- [gasps]
You couldn't sleep last night.
You'd better stay in my room.
Mmm-hmm.
I'll keep watch over Noah.
Go on.
[ANNE]
Thank you!
[crickets chirp]
[sighs]
[ANNE] He's protecting me
as though I'm a child.
But still,
I'm so happy.
[HERBERT]
Young Silver Sugar Master.
Huh?
[ANNE]
Am I dreaming?
Oh!
[NOAH]
Lord Herbert, it's your turn.
Huh?
[HERBERT]
Hmm.
Should I move here?
[NOAH]
Why's it taking you so long?
[ANNE]
Who is that?
Is he Noah's master?
Here, try one of these, Noah.
Would you?
That crest is such
a beautiful detail.
That's because it stands
for the pride of my family.
The lion, swords, and shield are
symbols of strength
and the blue flag
for compassion.
Its full meaning is,
"Follow me,
for I use my strength
to care for the people."
Even so, I don't know a thing
about wielding a sword.
Perhaps,
but you have a strong heart
instead Lord Herbert,
and you're extremely kind.
Forgive me for asking, sir
but why do you keep me here
when I'm so useless?
Don't be absurd!
You're far from useless.
[NOAH]
That isn't true!
I'm clumsy
and I'm always breaking dishes.
I've never been
of any help to you.
You help me quite often.
For example,
you are the only one who is
an equal opponent for me
when I'm playing a game.
You're just as bad at them
as I am,
it's much more fun that way.
Well, that may be true sir,
but I wouldn't really
consider it a compliment.
[HERBERT]
Well, perhaps you should.
[NOAH, HERBERT]
[laugh]
[thunder rumbles]
How can you just go off
and leave me!
Lord Herbert, please answer me!
[HERBERT]
I told you.
Until I can return home,
I need you to look after
the castle for me.
[NOAH]
Why me!
Anyone else could stay.
[HERBERT]
Here.
- Take these.
- [gasps]
I want you to eat them.
Huh?
If they found these,
they'd crush them to bits,
so I'd much rather have you
eat them instead.
Noah, please protect this place.
It's an important task
that only you can fulfil for me.
But listen,
don't eat anything else here
besides the confections
I just gave you.
Huh?
When you get hungry
and feel like eating something,
I would like for you to leave,
all right?
But why?
[NOAH gasps]
I don't understand at all!
Tell me.
[thunder rumbles]
[NOAH]
Then I won't eat these.
[sobs]
I refuse to.
[ANNE]
Noah...
[HERBERT]
I have a request of you,
young Silver Sugar Master.
Please find a way to save him.
[grunts]
What should I do?
Huh?
[rain patters]
It's raining?
At this time of year?
- [KING] In here! Quick!
- Huh?
[ORLAND]
The silver sugar!
[ANNE gasps]
It hardened!
What do we do now!
[VALENTINE]
This is completely solid!
[ORLAND]
These are, too.
[KING] They've absorbed
the humidity, as well.
[grunts] Check them all!
See what we can salvage!
Move them over there!
- [VALENTINE] Right!
- [NADIR] We're too late!
- The rain soaked through!
- [ORLAND] It's ruined.
[ELLIOTT] Blast it!
Every one of them is drenched!
- Oh, no! -This barrel is...
- This too.
How can this be?